PINKY: Ah, okay! Walking is great.
PINKY: But walking with THIS?
PINKY: Obviously better.
MAVILI: Cute.
PINKY: Hmm. Cute?
MAVILI: Mine has better stats.
MAVILI: Find equipment. Upgrade it. Get stronger.
PINKY: Wow.
PINKY: You discovered upgrading.
MAVILI: I was explaining it.
PINKY: You were explaining it very slowly.
PINKY: And when being powerful isn't enough, hmm?
PINKY: Well, you make sure everyone knows you're powerful.
MAVILI: Very humble.
PINKY: Thank you.
MAVILI: That wasn't a compliment.
PINKY: I know.
PINKY: And THIS is my reward showcase.
MAVILI: Hmm. So, basically,
MAVILI: Oh! A museum about yourself?
PINKY: Exactly!
PINKY: And admission is free.
PINKY: Walk. Fight. Earn better equipment.
MAVILI: Upgrade it.
PINKY: Unlock titles.
MAVILI: Collect rewards.
ALL: GET STRONGER.
PINKY: Heh! Although, I'm obviously stronger.
MAVILI: No, you're not.
PINKY: Yes, I am.
MAVILI: No. I'M stronger.
PINKY: Based on what?
MAVILI: Look at me.
PINKY: Hmm. I'm looking.
MAVILI: And?
PINKY: Still stronger.
MAVILI: No, I'M stronger!
PINKY: ME!
MAVILI: ME!
PINKY: Me!
MAVILI: Me!
PINKY: ME!
MAVILI: ME!
PINKY: I'm literally stronger!
MAVILI: According to who?
PINKY: ME!
MAVILI: We're checking the stats after this!
PINKY: Ha! Sure. Prepare to be disappointed.